<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_name_sentry">
        <item>Security Camera</item>
        <item>Recover</item>
        <item>Stun Trap</item>
        <item>Motion Sensor</item>
        <item>Lux Generator</item>
        <item>Frag Grenade</item>
        <item>Surveillance Bug</item>
        <item>Shock Rocket</item>
        <item>Search Drone</item>
        <item>Sprint</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cooldown_sentry">
        <item>6</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cost_sentry">
        <item>7</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_description_sentry">
        <item>Drop a security camera in current position that notifies you of position of other player within 7x7 area. The camera is visible to the other player within his proximity range. Effect does not stop until camera is destroyed.</item>
        <item>Gain an extra life.</item>
        <item>Place a stun trap in any adjacent tile. Other player will end current turn and skip next turn when trap is stepped on. You will be notified when trap is triggered.</item>
        <item>Set up a motion sensor in any adjacent tile. The sensor covers an area that is walkable up to 2 tiles away  from its current position, and is triggered each time other player move within its range. The sensor notifies you of the other player\'s position and also notify the other player of its trigger. Location of motion sensor is hidden until destroyed</item>
        <item>Drop a light-emitting generator at current position. This shows all constructs in the room and position of players to all players. Visibility is returned to normal upon destroying generator.</item>
        <item>Destroy all constructs, yours and other player\'s, in all adjacent tiles from target tile. Also, damages all players by 1 in the area of effect. Throwing range is within 5x5 grid with current position in center.</item>
        <item>Place a bug in current position that reveals all objects and the other player to you when in that location.</item>
        <item>Target any tile in room. If other player is in a 5x5 area from target tile, he skips his next turn.</item>
        <item>Reveals current position of other player in from any tile and any room.</item>
        <item>Move to any tile within a 5x5 area with current position as center. This move will fail if target tile is an obstacle</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_name_spy">
        <item>EMP Blast</item>
        <item>Drop Mine</item>
        <item>Drop Mine 2</item>
        <item>Drop Mine 3</item>
        <item>Plant Decoy</item>
        <item>Emergency Heal</item>
        <item>Deploy Barrier</item>
        <item>Illumination Beacon</item>
        <item>Snipe</item>
        <item>Shrapnel Blast</item>
        <item>Toxic Cloud</item>
        <item>Bait</item>
        <item>Sprint</item>
        <item>Surveillance Bug</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cooldown_spy">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cost_spy">
        <item>8</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_description_spy">
        <item>Removes all constructs in any target tile in the room, and all tiles to its left, to its right, above and below.</item>
        <item>Place a mine in current tile. Deals 1 damage to other when stepping on tile.</item>
        <item>Place a mine in current tile. Deals 1 damage to other when stepping on tile. Longer cooldown.</item>
        <item>Place a mine in current tile. Deals 1 damage to other when stepping on tile. Longest cooldown.</item>
        <item>Deploy a decoy in any adjacent tile. Decoy is visible to both players in the room.</item>
        <item>Gain an extra life, but will skip current and next turn. Very long cooldown.</item>
        <item>Place a barrier obstacle in any adjacent tile. Can be destroyed.</item>
        <item>Place an illumination beacon in current position or any adjacent tile. Shows all constructs and players to all within a 5x5 grid. Once beacon is destroyed, visibility is returned to normal</item>
        <item>Choose a target tile. If other player is in that tile, it deals 1 damage to him. Notifies you if other player was hit.</item>
        <item>Deal 1 damage to all players within any 5x5 grid with target tile as center</item>
        <item>Deal 1 damage to the other player if he is within 7x7 area, with current tile as center</item>
        <item>Reveal current position to the other player</item>
        <item>Move to any tile within a 5x5 area with current position as center. This move will fail if target tile contains an obstacle.</item>
        <item>Place a bug in current position that reveals all objects and the other player to you when in that location.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>