<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_name_sentry">
        <item>Alarm Trap</item>
        <item>Extra Life</item>
        <item>Stun Mine</item>
        <item>Motion Sensor</item>
        <item>Frag Grenade</item>
        <item>Room Illumination Beacon</item>
        <item>Night Vision Googles</item>
        <item>Shock Grenade</item>
        <item>Search Drone</item>
        <item>Sprint</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cooldown_sentry">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cost_sentry">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_description_sentry">
        <item>Drop an alarm trap in current position that shows position of other player within 5x5 area. Other player is notified that this trap has been triggered.</item>
        <item>(Passive) Gain an extra life</item>
        <item>Place a stun mine in any tile next to current position. Other player will end current turn and skip next turn when tile with mine is stepped on.</item>
        <item>Set up a motion sensor in a 3x3 area from current position, that notifies you of the other player's position. Note, this will not notify the other player of its trigger.</item>
        <item>Drop a beacon in current position that shows all skill items in the room and position of players to all players. Visibility is returned to normal upon destroying beacon.</item>
        <item>Destroy all skill items, yours and other player's, in all adjacent tiles from target tile. Also, damages all players by 1 in the area of effect</item>
        <item>Reveal position of all objects and other player in a straight line from current position to target tile</item>
        <item>Target any tile in room. If other player is in a 5x5 area from target tile, he skips his next turn.</item>
        <item>Reveals current position of other player in from any tile and any room.</item>
        <item>Move to any tile within a 5x5 area with current position as center. This move will fail if target tile is an obstacle</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_name_spy">
        <item>EMP Blast</item>
        <item>Drop Mine</item>
        <item>Drop Mine 2</item>
        <item>Drop Mine 3</item>
        <item>Plant Decoy</item>
        <item>Extra Life</item>
        <item>Deploy Barrier</item>
        <item>Illumination Beacon</item>
        <item>Snipe</item>
        <item>Shrapnel Blast</item>
        <item>Toxic Cloud</item>
        <item>Bait</item>
        <item>Sprint</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cooldown_spy">
        <item>4</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="chase_array_skill_select_cost_spy">
        <item>4</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="chase_array_skill_select_description_spy">
        <item>Removes all skill items in the room within a 3x3 grid from target tile as center.</item>
        <item>Place a mine in current tile. Deals 1 damage to other when stepping on tile.</item>
        <item>Place a mine in current tile. Deals 1 damage to other when stepping on tile. Longer cooldown.</item>
        <item>Place a mine in current tile. Deals 1 damage to other when stepping on tile. Longest cooldown.</item>
        <item>Deploy a decoy in any adjacent tile. Decoy is visible to both players in the room.</item>
        <item>(Passive) Gain an extra life</item>
        <item>Place a barrier obstacle in any adjacent tile. Can be destroyed.</item>
        <item>Place a beacon in current position</item>
        <item>Choose a target tile. If other player is in that tile, it deals 1 damage to him.</item>
        <item>Deal 1 damage to all players within any 5x5 grid with target tile as center</item>
        <item>Deal 1 damage to the other player if he is within 7x7 area, with current tile as center</item>
        <item>Reveal current position to the other player</item>
        <item>Move to any tile within a 5x5 area with current position as center. This move will fail if target tile contains an obstacle.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>